Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING THE FILMING
OF THIS PRODUCTION
You will drown in the revenge of
Turks, Subutay.
Run to the tempting arms of death, Osman!
Die!
I am not going to leave this wicked Tent
before I skin you off.
So you decided to haunt our Tent, huh?
Our Tent...
...is going to become your graveyard.
Subutay.
Sofia.
You took two of my children away from me.
Now, it is time to pay for what you did.
Bamsı Bey!
Calm down, Bamsı Bey.
Gündüz Bey will take care of her.
Bamsı Bey!
Take this serpent away!
Keep her wait in the cage till Gündüz Bey
beheads her.
Go now!
Keep an eye on this dog.
Brother.
Let's leave.
Bamsı Bey!
Sofia!
Göktuğ.
Spare me some water.
Instead of dying off your shame, you are
asking for water without any honor.
Water…
…I asked you to give me water.
Do you want me to die of thirst?
Göktuğ.
My...
...my Valiant brother.
Göktuğ.
Kongar has never left anything half done.
Your time has come.
Alps!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
Are you okay?
Don't mind me.
Sofia has just ran away.
Go and find her!
Come on!
Faster!
My Valiants.
His condition is very bad.
Osman…
…not a single one but may thousands of
vassals die for your path.
Oh, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Brother.
-Is the physician from Söğüt here?
-Yes, he is here. My brother.
Let's take him to the dispensary as soon
as possible.
Come on Alps!
Stay strong, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Come on!
Halt!
We have lost everything, Balgay.
There is no time to talk, woman!
They will be here soon.
They ran away.
What are we going to tell our Bey?
Let’s follow them.
To the horses!
Don’t give up, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
Take a look at him.
Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Stay strong.
He lost a lot of blood, my Bey.
Is Abdurrahman Ghazi going to make it?
Tell me that now!
Only my Rab knows that.
However, for Alps like Abdurrahman,
there is something much worse.
Do whatever it takes to keep him
alive, Physician.
Do whatever it takes!
Then, we need to amputate his arm.
- What are you talking about, physician?
- What are you saying?
What are you talking
about?
That arm...
... serves as the wings
covering our customs.
That arm took many heads.
Do you think to cut that off
is arm is something easy to do?
Do you really think that?
My Bey, I know it’s not easy.
But if we don’t cut the arm, he will
get necrosis and die, my Bey.
His arm needs to be cut and stigmatized.
He will not make it and eventually die.
We need to cut it!
Physician, do anything you need to make...
... Abdurrahman Ghazi will
leave this place alive.
With or without his arm.
Make Abdurrahman Ghazi
leave this place alive.
Only if Allah allows us.
Abdurrahman Gazi.
Göktuğ.
May the tips of your wings not get broken.
"May the tips of your wings
not get broken."
May Allah never let you in need of
he who is despicable.
"May Allah never let you in need of
he who is despicable."
How is Abdurrahman holding up, son?
Not good, mother.
Physician says he may not make it.
What are you saying, son?
Isn’t there another way to save him?
Even if he lives,
his arm needs to be amputated.
From now on,
Abdurrahman Ghazi is handicapped.
Osman!
Come here!
Göktuğ...
My brother Göktuğ...
May the tips of your wings not get broken.
Göktuğ...
Don't.
Brothers, don't...
- Brother!
- Don't.
Brother! What did I do?
Brother!
Help! I beg you!
Please, don't.
Osman!
Face me, Osman!
Stop talking to your women and come here!
Come here, Osman!
Come.
How dare you tie me up, Osman!
Untie my hands!
So that I can show you
the power of Mongols!
Well done, Osman.
Well done.
You're brave.
Come here.
Let's see how you fight.
Where is Geyhatu?
Why does he send dogs like you
instead of coming here himself?
Tell me!
Geyhatu will come.
Don't worry.
He's coming back for Baydu.
He'll come for you.
Baydu!
If you're a man,
show me what you can do first.
The Turk is angry!
The dog is angry!
But he'll see!
All of you! All of you will see
the power of the Mongols!
Before we see it...
... you should first...
... taste Osman's slap!
Is this the power of the Mongols?
Is this the reign you're showing off?
Tell me!
Where are the others?
Only we're left, Balgay.
We don't have much time.
Let's go to the castle, Balgay.
We shouldn't lose any more time.
- Everything is over.
- Nothing is over until I'm dead, Sofia.
I will not die until I end them.
Let's go to the castle.
I'll show you the fate of these lands.
Those who come to invade...
... will go as they came.
You ran away here
because you were scared of us.
What changed?
We came again.
We found you again.
We'll be the ones who end you.
We came to this lands...
... to spread Allah's religion.
We came for a holy war!
We came to destroy your
reign of oppression!
Do you think it will end
because you killed everyone?
We'll swarm this place.
We'll come for blood,
for revenge!
Let Alişar's death be an example
to the cruel among us.
And also yours...
... to every cruel...
- Long live, Osman Bey!
- Allahu Akbar!
Send this dog's head to Geyhatu.
He shall see what will happen to him.
Stop!
Don't eat the food!
This traitor poisoned the food!
Eat it.
You dog!
I'll kill those who try to harm us!
Come, son. I'll check your
wound at the tent.
Don't worry. I'm okay.
You're worried because Osman
gets one victory after the other.
Don't, mother.
They're trying to take my father's throne.
But I won't let this go. I won't let Osman
be the Bey while my father is still here.
Know that.
It's not about Osman, son.
It's the upcoming disaster.
We'll get rid of Osman.
But...
... Geyhatu will come.
Osman went too far this time.
Subutay was Geyhatu's right hand.
- He took his life.
- He deserved it, mother.
He did. But Geyhatu will be furious
after hearing about this.
Then he'll attack Kayıs with his army.
Our duty is to save Kayıs from this, son.
There is only one person
who will and can do this.
- My uncle.
- That's right.
You'll go to him.
You'll inform him about what happened.
People in the Tent don't need to know
about where you're going.
I'll tell them he went to thank
his brother for the intel.
Tell him everything thoroughly.
So that he can think of a solution
for the upcoming storm.
Osman won't let Subutay live.
Osman will make Geyhatu come here himself.
He won't come, woman! He won't!
After Konya, he went back.
So, Osman could attack your castle
any second now.
We don't hear from Kongar either.
Are you really thinking about Kongar now?
Tell me, how did Osman
find out about the ambush?
Balgay this, Balgay that.
How should I know?
I came to save your life
and you're questioning me.
Who are they?
My executioners who will destroy Osman.
We'll find remedies for our veterans
after we bury our martyrs.
We'll get the Tent on its feet again.
We're responsible for relieving
the Tent's wounds.
These eyes saw many things...
We'll get through this eventually.
We should look for damages and losses.
The rest is easy, with Allah's help.
Aygül! My arm hurts!
Why are you squeezing it?
What? Are you okay?
Hazal Hatun.
We suffered too much from our conflicts.
My opinions about you were biased
because of this. I'm sorry.
I was unfair to you.
Well, you weren't wrong, Selcan.
Your eyes saw such betrayals.
You'll protect your Tent. Of course.
But now you very well know who is who.
As long as we're together,
we'll take care of the rest.
If Allah permits.
Why are you knitting your eyebrows?
There's blood everywhere.
It won't wash off.
These days will pass, Aygül.
Don't be upset.
It will be over.
Dündar Bey...
Bamsı Bey...
- Am I okay?
- The Physician is here.
Don't tire yourself, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
He'll do everything necessary.
Don't tire yourself.
How is my arm doing?
We need to cut it.
There is no other way.
Dündar Bey!
Bamsı Bey!
We swing our swords with our hearts,
not arms!
Bless you!
Tevekkeltü Tealallah
[I trust in Allah]
My Osman...
Stay!
Stay, Dündar Bey!
Witness it!
Witness it.
Abdurrahman Gazi, the friend of Kayıs...
... will sacrifice his arm in the name
of Allah without batting an eye!
We're witnesses, Abdurrahman Gazi.
We're witnesses.
Witness me, dear Allah!
Abdurrahman Ghazi!
We grew up with your tales of war.
Hold on!
How could I let you go easily,
Abdurrahman Ghazi?
My brother...
Hold on.
My brother!
Physician!
Do it!
Cut my arm off!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.]
Dear Allah...
Ya Allah!
You're living in an imaginary
world, Sofia.
Osman killed my Nökers and your knights.
Will these take our revenge?
This is a spell.
They are possessed, Cerkutay.
They sold their souls to the devil.
Not to the devil...
... to my father.
The secret which removed their fear of
death is hidden in the potion they drank.
What if they're not afraid?
Won't they die?
Of course they die.
But they don't feel pain!
Dark knights continue fighting as long
as they don't have fatal wounds.
What kind of a potion is this?
Why didn't you tell me before?
My father completed it on his last days.
He didn't have time to tell me
how he did it.
Pity.
Yannis is no more.
But the potion is here.
I want some of it.
Unfortunately, it's impossible.
We've used the last bottle.
The effects will continue for a few days.
That means we don't have much
time to kill Osman.
What will happen when
the potion wears out?
The effects won't wear out.
They will change.
It will turn into poison and kill them.
Osman, who doesn't fear death,
will fight the dead.
Balgay liked this.
Knights!
Brother!
We should let him rest. He shouldn't
be in the middle of everything.
I'll take one life
for each drop of his blood!
If not for Hazal Hatun, we'd
have many more casualties.
It's obvious. But...
How did Çobanoğulları
know about this ambush?
Son, it seems their
intelligence is strong.
This is suspicious, Bamsı Bey.
My shame is enough for me, nephew.
If you have suspicions, tell me.
Thanks to them, the Tent
was ready for the attack.
I was there at the last minute.
But, if they knew
about the attack earlier...
... it means they are seeing us,
watching us, uncle.
There is more to this.
Sofia has escaped, my Bey!
How did she escape, speak!
Balgay came, my Bey,
they escaped together.
Only place for them to
hide is the castle.
Now is the time to take them out
of the castle and end them!
How will we do this, brother?
As long as they are in that castle,
there's no rest for us.
I've sent my Alps to take Konur
and Dumrul. They haven't returned.
After Göktuğ comes here...
... we'll see what we can do.
Let's go.
What is he doing here?
How could that coward come here!
Stop, my Bey. Göktuğ brought news.
He could've killed both
of us if he wanted to.
How many faces, heads
are there above your shoulders?
Speak!
Balgay put a spell on me.
You, vile coward!
How many times we'll
belive you, how many will die?
Balgay poisoned me, he stole my soul.
He made me hurt my brothers!
Stop, Bamsı Bey.
Bamsı Bey...
Bamsı Bey, don't.
Don't do this, my Bey.
Don't, Bamsı Bey.
Go, take Konur to medical tent.
Osman Bey, let me stay with my brother.
If something happens to him,
bury my body under his feet.
Boran, watch him closely.
If he tries to do something.
Kill him.
As you command, my Bey.
- How are you, son?
- I'm good, father.
My Bahadır is well, thank Allah.
But you, are you okay, my Bey?
I am alive. I am alive.
But I'm not well.
We've overcome a disaster.
Now is the time to recover.
We'll be okay, don't you worry.
Hazal, I have a question,
but I can't find the answer.
Tell me, how did your brother
know about the ambush when...
... we could not?
My brother knows everything going on in
this region, Dündar Bey, don't you know?
They say Yavlak Hasan doesn't sleep,
father. He's always watching.
If he doesn't, his men will, if they
don't, wolves and birds tell him.
Thanks to them for this.
But this is only our issue now.
I agree, my Bey. But since he
gave us the information...
... we need to thank my brother for that.
I say Bahadır goes there.
He can see his uncle...
... and give Kayı Tent's
gratitude and greetings to him.
What do you say, my Bey?
Your mother is right,
son, go to Çobanoğulları.
Tell them that Kayıs stand strong.
But they should know, this is
our issue from now on.
Tell them that.
I will, father.
Let's go, you should take
your Bey's permission.
Let's go and tell Gündüz Bey.
It will pass, don't worry.
You showed mercy, brother.
But how can we trust that Göktuğ?
Son, Gündüz is right. Our
mercy could bring us trouble.
Don't you worry.
He will give us Sofia and Balgay.
Gündüz Bey, if you allow us,
Bahadır will go on a journey.
What is it, uncle?
We should thank
Muzaffereddin Yavlak Hasan.
And they could see each other.
Uncle and nephew.
You thought well, uncle.
Bahadır, give my regards to your uncle.
We will return his kindness, surely.
He knows that we neither forget kinship...
... nor rivalry.
As you say, Osman Bey,
I will give your regards to him.
My Bey, I will go if you'll excuse me.
My wish was to bring
my brother to the Tent.
I brought him.
Now, It's hard for me to live.
Good, you can still feel shame then.
From now on, my blood and life is yours.
If you want, I will bring
Balgay's head to you.
Or you can take my head instead.
Your call.
My life is yours only.
Your brother's head always looked up.
Göktuğ!
Lift your head up.
You won't give your life for us.
You will give it for your brother.
Aygül, come here girl.
This madness of her is
enough already, but...
... we'll see.
May your enemies froze, may your
arrows find their target, my Bey.
Amin.
Amin, Hatun.
Sofia is an old enemy.
They caused our Tent so much trouble.
And you, and my Sheikh...
... you faced death by their hands.
It's time to answer for their crimes.
It's not only Sofia, Balgay is also there.
The fight will be hard, my Bey.
Köni, Subutay, Balgay,
Geyhatu, and then...
... another tyrant.
The fight won't be over
until life ends, Hatun.
Then, may Allah give you long life.
Long may you live, my Osman.
May many victories be yours.
May you live a long life too, so that...
... I can return to your side, Hatun.
May Allah protect you.
You too, my Osman. May Allah guide you.
Even if you do, I won't forgive myself.
If something happens to you,
brother, how could I live with that?
Göktuğ, don't say that.
Göktuğ.
I have neither gold...
... nor wealth or property.
My only heritage to you is
my loyalty to Osman Bey.
Brother. Don't talk like that.
May you become a valiant Alp of Osman Bey.
We'll take revenge with
Osman Bey, brother.
We are going to take
that dog's head for you.
My Bey.
You are going to fight, huh?
My Konur...
Without me!
You recover first.
We have conquests to have.
Don't worry at all.
I will avenge you.
I will rip the hearts of...
...those who hurt you.
You just hold your horses, brother.
Don't you dare...
Don't...
...leave me without my Konur.
Konur, your face glowed when you heard
about conquest and jihad, my valiant.
He is my Konur. He can bear it.
I know he can. With Allah's help.
Bamsı Bey.
May you live long!
Göktuğ.
It's time.
Duty calls.
My life is yours, Osman Bey.
Give me your blessing, brother.
My blessing is yours.
Every bit of it.
Brother.
My blessing is yours.
Is yours mine, too?
Tell me.
Of course, my Bey.
And may Allah bless us all.
Bamsı Beyrek.
May you live long.
Thank you, my Bey.
Balgay thinks that I'm on
the road of Konya with Boran.
He will come after us for Genghis'
relic.
Bamsı Bey. Your mission is watching our
back against Sofia.
Our eyes, ears, and hearts are with you...
...with the help of Allah, my Bey.
For our cause, martyrs, gazis...
...and for...
...all the innocents.
May Allah help us.
May Allah accompany us.
My Osman.
Come on, warriors.
Giddyap!
My son!
Are you alright, my son?
What have they done to you?
I killed that dog called Konur.
I hardly escaped from their hands.
Don't worry, my son. I will skin them
alive! Skin them all alive!
Osman will take the Genghis' Laws...
...to Geyhatu.
-Osman!
-He will have only one warrior with him.
Only two of them.
You will get better, Kongar.
You will be healed.
What are you waiting for, woman?
Don't you have a healer?
Hurry, take him to the physician.
Don't worry. Don't worry, Kongar.
You will be healed.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hurry up!
Hurry up! Come on! Hurry!
Those Laws belongs to me, not Geyhatu.
Those relics are my right!
-Bring my horse!
-We'll go together. I'm coming with you.
Were you with me under the frost of
steppes or the heat of deserts, woman?
I will take the revenge of my son
on my own.
Don't push your luck, Sofia.
Bear of the steppe is after his revenge.
I won't leave Osman to him.
Tell the knights to get ready at once.
We are leaving.
I will wash my hands with the blood
of Osman.
We did what we could.
But the wound is infected.
If you have anything to say,
we don't have much time.
Konur...
Brother...
Hang in there.
You can't go like this.
My Bey.
Göktuğ...
Protect him.
My valiant, my valiant.
We'll have many jihads to have.
We will have many jihads.
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah...
...and I bear witness that Muhammad is...
...the servant and Messenger of Allah.
To take roots in these lands...
...what prices had we paid, uncle?
Konur...
...now, no one can take us
apart from here.
No one.
I won't leave you alone in this fight...
...for my brother Kongar, I'm coming.
As Kongar said, he knows what will
happen to him if he goes with all his...
...men, he took only one of them with
him.
They move slowly because of the
gifts they carry to Geyhatu.
They will stop somewhere,
before the sun fall.
Then, their flesh will open.
Land will spew blood.
Valiants who passed away for homeland...
...lost their lives and gained
a reputation.
This reputation is called martyrdom.
They accompany Hz. Hamza in the heaven.
-Give your blessings to them.
-Our blessings are upon them.
It is our warriors who made these
lands our home.
The warriors who fought to spread
one true faith, and the law of Turks.
Ones who forget their martyrs, forget
their laws.
Kayı's valiants, sisters! Don't forget!
If we are here, it is because of them.
Allahu Ekber. Allahu Ekber.
Take Zöhre Hatun to Kuluca Hisar
walls.
If she served them, she should listen...
...the sounds of bells on the other world.
May Allah pardon her deeds.
Aygül!
Sister!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
La ilahe illallah!
(There is no deity but Allah.)
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
This is good.
Boran.
Look sharp.
We are going to have a guest.
Let it be, my Bey.
Sofia, run!
Run as fast as you can.
But you should know that
you are going to...
see my face while you are dying.
Osman strikes again.
Protect Princess!
My Bey, what is this?
We take refuge in the name of Allah.
We take refuge from the accursed Satan.
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Osman thinks he has tricked us with Kongar.
Balgay will need us.
We are not in a hurry.
Vuka! Come with me.
- Sofia is running, Bamsı Bey.
- I see, Dumrul, I see.
Let's do it, valiants!
Let's crush them!
We shall not let Osman be alone!
Let's do it, valiants!
Mother...
I wish you were here with my brother.
Aygül is alone.
Aygül can't be sad.
We'll get through.
Don't be sad.
I will complete this, mother.
Surround them.
Let them get stuck in here.
Today, we take blood, Cerkutay.
Sun shall be red.
Alps!
They are not humans, Bamsı Bey.
They are not!
How are we going to deal
with them, my Bey?
No, sons.
Do not lose hope.
La ya'lemu'l-ğaybe illallah.
(Only Allah knows the future)
Bang your swords in these devils' hearts!
Allah-u Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Gather rope and needles, my beautiful
daughter.
We need to repair the tents.
I did, Hazal Hatun.
I told the girls about this.
They will tell us how many tents
we have to darn.
Then, we are going to start working
with Hatuns.
They married in a hurry.
They have sacrificed a lot recently.
They wasted the new bride.
We'll get through this.
Don't be sad.
Hatuns! There are too many damaged tents
in the downtown. We need to fix them.
We can gather sedge. If we act together,
we can darn it in two days.
You are right, my daughter.
Take Hatuns and do it.
The doctor who came for our woundeds
is good. He'll cure them inshaallah.
- Inshaallah.
Aygül?
What is happening?
This is a nice day to die, Osman.
Then we can welcome you in the...
Turk's table of death, Balgay.
Come on, Balgay.
Kongar.
Kongar is dead.
Göktuğ returned for you.
Treason.
You betrayed me.
We don't hunt birds.
We feed them.
How can you do that to me?
You were like a son to me!
I took your soul!
How can you do that to me?
I am armed with my mother's lullaby
and shahada, elhamdulillah(thank Allah).
You stole my soul.
You took my mother, father, brother.
And I will take your filthy heart today.
Come on then.
Both of you...
shall die.
Allah is eternal!
Die, son of devil, die!
Aygül, don't, my sister.
Give that dagger to me.
We'll get through this, don't be sad.
Aygül!
Aygül, daughter. Aygül.
Go away! You accepted The Dark Sultan
in your place!
Everybody's gone, Aygül is left alone!
You are not alone, my daughter.
There's Bala.
Your father is here.
Also Burçin is here.
Don't do it.
Everywhere is in blood.
We can't clean it!
You did it!
Aygül, look...
your father...
would be very sad, don't do it.
I have no father, no mother, no brother.
I don't have anyone!
No, my daughter, no. You have a father
who would sacrifice everything for you
Don't do it.
Enough!
First, you took my dignity.
Then, my son.
Göktuğ has found himself.
I will burn you all, Osman.
I will wipe you out.
Boran.
You'll pay for your betrayal, Kongar.
Göktuğ...
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ.
Are you okay, brother?
I won't die before those ignobles, my Bey.
He'll be killed...
with our holy swords, Göktuğ!
Now, it's time.
I wanted to be a bride...
and wear a wedding dress.
I wanted to! But...
They wanted power.
They sacrificed me.
They burned me!
Aygül.
They nearly killed me.
They took my brother.
Now, this Sultan took my mother!
There's blood everywhere!
My turn will come.
I know.
You can't see.
You can't.
I see the darkness.
This cruel Sultan will do
whatever it takes.
I see it.
She deceived all of you.
But she can't touch me!
- Daughter.
- Move!
My beautiful daughter.
My beautiful child.
I did...
It's my fault.
Come on. Kill me, daughter.
Move! I said move!
Kill me, daughter.
I'm guilty.
Kill me if it calms you down.
Come on.
- Come on, daughter.
- Move!
Don't, Aygül.
I'll be so sorry.
I can't take care of
your baby if I'm sorry.
I haven't fed him yet.
Let's feed him together.
Do you hear it?
Your baby is crying.
He wants you, Aygül.
Come on.
Come on, daughter.
Take care of the baby.
I'll kill this woman!
What did you do?!
What did you do?! What did you do?
What did you do?
What did you do? Everything was
going to be okay!
What did you do?
Everything was
going to be okay!
What did you do?!
Everything was going to be okay!
Osman.
My Osman.
Ya Allah!
Are you okay, brother?
Hold on, valiants!
Bamsı Bey.
They nearly killed all of us, my Bey.
I know, son.
I know.
Now, go to the tent.
Inform Gündüz Bey and Dündar Bey.
I'll go to Osman.
I won't leave my Osman alone.
Come on, valiants! Come on!
Come on!
Everything was going to be okay!
What did you do?
What did you do?!
Aygül.
- Aygül!
- What did you do?!
Don't cry.
Don't cry, my beautiful girl.
- Don't cry.
- Move!
Aygül.
I always wanted a daughter like you.
I don't have a daughter.
Willowy like you...
Beautiful like you...
Will you...
be my daughter, Aygül?
Can I?
Yes.
You can.
I'll say that Aygül is my daughter...
...that she is my child.
Aygül...
All the world hear that...
Aygül is my daughter.
And I'm her mother, I'll say!
Okay?
Aygül!
Daughter!
Osman Bey.
Let me do it.
I want to take revenge on my mother
and father.
I loved you like my child.
And you'll kill me as if I'm a dog.
Your love is like your courage.
It's a lie!
Die, dog!
Göktuğ.
Göktuğ!
Osman!
Just in time, Sofia.
Yoı betrayed Geyhatu
and then my father...
and then me and Osman, Balgay.
You don't deserve to live.
Right, Osman Bey?
If someone rebels...
that someone dies.
Perfidious!
Nice.
You saved me from trouble.
Osman...
Like Bamsı and his Alps on my way.
They are dead.
You should give in!
Don't you still
know that Turks don't give in?
I'll see you when you're out of breath.
If someone who's out of breath dies...
for the Allah's sake...
Allah-u Akbar! (Allah is the greatest!)
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries